This is Superman. [IMG:left]
This is Shazam. [IMG:right]
So, what's the difference? [IMG:wtd]
Superman is a Kryptonian who [IMG:speak_left]
was born with incredible powers [IMG:speak_left]
under Earth's yellow sun. [IMG:speak_left]
Shazam is an ordinary kid [IMG:speak_left]
who transforms into a magical [IMG:speak_left]
superhero by saying, Shazam. [IMG:speak_left]
Superman's abilities come from alien [IMG:speak_left]
biology, while Shazam's powers are [IMG:speak_left]
granted by ancient magic. [IMG:speak_left]
That's why magic is one [IMG:remember_this]
of Superman's biggest weaknesses, but [IMG:remember_this]
it's the source of Shazam's strength. [IMG:remember_this]
Superman is powered by the [IMG:speak_left]
sun, while Shazam is powered [IMG:speak_left]
by magic. [IMG:final_end]